[Mayor Johnson]: Spring Hill Board of Mayor and Aldermen
will come to order.
[Mayor Johnson]: Let the record show it's July 21st at 6:00 p.m.
[Mayor Johnson]: Let the record show that all the members
are present.
[Mayor Johnson]: We will begin tonight with Mr. Eric Drook
from Christ Chapel Church.
[Mr. Drook]: Thank you, Mayor. Let us bow our heads
in prayer.
[Mr. Drook]: Amen.
[Mayor Johnson]: Thank you, Mr. Drook.
Please proceed with the Pledge of Allegiance.
[ALL]: I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States
of America, and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty
and justice for all.
[Mayor Johnson]: Thank you. Next we have public comments.
Is there anyone who would like to address the board?
[Citizen Smith]: Yes, Mayor. I'd like to speak about
the proposed zoning changes on Main Street.